// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Immersing Yourself Mindfully In Nature Is Known In Japan As 'Shinrin-Yoku'. What Does This Lterally Mean?",
    answer: "Forest Bathing",
    options: [
      "Forest Bathing",
      "Going Green",
      "Returning To Your Roots",
      "enchanting"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It's Loved To Recycle Plastic That's Dirty,Low Value Or Mis-Sorted .So,Even Through Many Of Us Out Over Plastic Waste In The Blue Bin,What Percentage Of It Actually Gets Recycled?S",
    answer: "Around 9%",
    options: [
      "Around 30%",
      "Around 50%",
      "Around 9%",
      "Around 22%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Globally,2020 Was The Hottedt Year So Far On Record?",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
    "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "So,Far How Many Mass Exinction Events Have There Been In Earth's History?",
    answer: "Five",
    options: [
      "One",
      "None",
      "Five",
      "Ten"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In What Year Did The First Earth Take Place?",
    answer: "1970",
    options: [
      "1970",
      "1980",
      "1996",
      "1974"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who Is Called The Father Of Earth Day?",
    answer: "Gaylord Nelson",
    options: [
      "Wangari Maathai",
      "Mark Boyle",
      "Vandana Shiva",
      "Gaylord Nelson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which Is A More Appropriate Reason To Observe The Earth Day Every Yesr?",
    answer: "To Support For Environmental Protection",
    options: [
      "To Save The Ozone Layer",
      "To Protect The Species",
      "To Support For Environmental Protection",
      "None Of The Above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How Much Oxygen Does An Average 50 Year Old Tree Provides?",
    answer: "Enough For 4 Person",
    options: [
      "Enough For 4 Person",
      "Enough For 1 Person",
      "Enough For 8 Person",
      "Enough For 10 Person"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What Was The Purpose Of The National Environmental Education Act Passed By Congress In 1990?",
    answer: "To require that the united states environmental protection agency be a leader in promoting environmental literacy.",
    options: [
      "To establish the office of environmental education.",
      "To require that the united states environmental protection agency be a leader in promoting environmental literacy.",
      "Both a&b",
      "None Of the above"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which Land Based Ecosystem Holds the most biodiversity i.e. concentration of plants and animals?",
    answer: "Tropical Forest",
    options: [
      "South Pacific Island",
      "African Savannah",
      "Tropical Forest",
      "Coral Reefs"
    ]
  },

];